Thank you.
Oh
Ah!
Gomorrah, what are you doing?
You're gonna knock us off if
you keep crashing like that!
Whoa!
Maybe he's too injured to go on.
What? No!
Gomorrah can't see!
His retinas were damaged
in that last attack.
He's blind!
What's that? Gomorrah!
You can't see anything?
It started running like crazy.
Don't just stand there, shoot it!
We gotta stop that thing.
We can't let it go any further!
Fire the transporter.
Gomorrah, don't do this. Please stop.
You're in no shape to go on.
You'll kill yourself.
He said that he made a promise.
To Sodom.
He told Sodom.
Leave the rest to me!
I'll take on your share and carry
everyone the rest of the way!
Gomorrah!
They were in its stomach?
I'm full already.
Couldn't eat another bite.
Let's take him with us as backup food.
Big bro! Come here quick!
Some pirates gave Sodom and
Gomorrah a serious beating!
Pirates have got a lot of nerve.
Never touch my family!
Hey!
Take it easy, you two!
You're still injured!
This is no time for a dance party!
Oh!
We're headed straight for a dead end!
He'll crash into it and die!
Gomorrah! Stop him!
You'll never make it! Stop!
Dead end?
I don't see one, do you?
Nope.
Can't say I see anything of the sort.
It's the courthouse!
He did it! Yeah!
You made it!
You wore it!
All units, the King Bull carrying
the pirates broke through Block D,
and they are now at the Courthouse Plaza.
I repeat, the King Bull carrying
the pirates broke through.
Look at this, Fogfreed.
A golden transponder snail.
Having this little gadget is the same as
having the authority
to issue a Buster Call.
That means I have the same
power as a Navy Admiral,
or someone even higher up than that.
Admiral Aokiji entrusted it to me.
The question is, if
and when will I use it?
Hmm.
Just you wait.
Once I revive the ancient weapons,
this won't just be something
that's on loan to me.
I'll carry it of my own accord, along
with the power to control an army.
With a single push of a button,
an entire island will disappear.
Authority can be a weapon unto itself.
Oh, the power.
Team Spandam!
That was close!
What's wrong with you?
Can't you even knock?
I almost accidentally hit the button!
I'm terribly sorry, sir, but I'm
afraid we've got an emergency here.
There's an urgent call from
Enies Lobby's main island.
Idiots!
If there's an emergency, why didn't
they just call my room directly?
What the?
Hey, why is the receiver off the hook?
This always happens.
Who's responsible?
Well, either way, you were saying
something about an emergency, weren't you?
Yes, sir.
Spanda.
Hey, Miss Robin,
it seems we have an urgent report coming
in from the Marines
down at the main island.
Knowing what it's likely about, I
wouldn't call it an emergency, exactly.
Your friends tried their best, but only
managed to take down five of our soldiers.
I wonder how they were
ultimately defeated.
Did some of my other men bring them down?
Or was it the giant gatekeeping
team of Oimo and Kashi?
So many possibilities.
Why don't we listen to the report?
About those idiots who
defied the world government?
and learn their fate together?
You're such a scumbag!
Shut up, you lowlife!
This is Spandam.
I understand you have a report.
Chiefs spawned him, finally!
Thank goodness!
I tried your direct line,
but I couldn't get through!
I'm...
I'm not really sure where to begin!
Calm down, take it easy!
It's the Straw Hats, right?
Yes, what about them?
Whoa, hold on!
Listen, just pick up from
where your last report ended.
Give me the gritty details,
loudly and clearly!
Right, the intruders - Did
you accidentally kill them?
Pity, it's their fault
for being such weaklings!
The intruders consist of about 60 pirates!
They've pushed their way
all the way through the
main island and have reached
the courthouse plaza.
We can't stop them, sir!
All personnel on Enies Lobby's main island
head to the courthouse plaza immediately!
You did a good job, Gomorrah.
I swear everything you two
did will not be in vain.
All right, we're breaking in!
It's time to say big bro breaking!
Yeah!
I repeat!
The Pirates have reached
the Courthouse Plaza!
Can you see Luffy?
Nope.
But whether he's up on the roof or not,
it's not exactly like we
can just jump up after him.
That's true.
How much we can do.
How many members of CP9
did you see up there?
It was just that one big
guy with the bullhorns.
It's hard to believe that Robin, Franky,
all of them are right behind those doors.
In any case, we need
to catch up with Luffy.
Then we can save Robin together! Hurry!
Get to the courthouse!
The draw break isn't down yet!
Corner them!
Whoa!
That frog's awesome!
That's the same ball
that took out Gomorrah!
Who threw it?
Whoa!
There's three of them!
And they're running away!
Why are they running away?
They're the ones that attacked first!
Idiot cook!
We can't go around chasing every
enemy that runs off like that!
It's a waste of time!
Oh, pipe down. It's confirmation.
Some of them need to
be chased, understand?
To find out who we're up against.
Who is this guy?
He must have superhuman strength to
swing something like that around.
You think he's part of some
special unit like those guard dogs?
There are probably more of them
hiding out there somewhere.
Let's be careful.
We need to get moving.
It looks like the
reinforcements have arrived.
Surround them!
There's no way they'll be able
to open those heavy stone doors!
We'll have them cornered!
Move it!
He's right.
Now that I think about it, how...
Are we gonna open those big stones?
We're going in first!
Stay close, don't fall behind! He...
he cut right through them!
Like it was nothing!
Hey, Samba!
Let's split up!
We need to charge both of those towers!
Because each side has a lever
to open up that drawbridge!
Yeah!
Good thinking! I'm on it! Right!
Looks like we need to
split into three teams!
Most of you go with Kiwi and
Mozu, the rest are with me!
We'll crack some heads in that courthouse!
Good luck, everyone! Move!
Ahhhhhhh!
Huh?
Also,
the gatekeepers of the main
island front gate, Oimo and Kashi,
have joined up with the pirates!
They're currently destroying the
central part of the main island!
We are the way!
After hearing all the field reports,
our guard casualties total
must be over 2,000 men!
Wait, not five?
And the man who took down over
1,000 of those men all by himself,
the notorious Straw Hat Luffy,
has suddenly disappeared!
We're still assessing the situation here!
In the history of this island, this is
without a doubt the absolute worst thing?
And it never happened in any slobby!
It's Bluno.
What's he doing out there on that rooftop?
What's happening here?
And why now?
What the hell's going on?
Baskerville!
Chief Justice Baskerville!
Come in! It's me!
Oh, hello, Chief Spottom.
This is left, Baskerville, on the left.
This is right, Baskerville, on the right.
And located in the center,
it is none other than I.
Central freeway closed for repair.
Oh, shut up!
Just give me a status report, dammit!
Is it true that the intruders have
made it to the Courthouse Plaza or not?
Let's see.
A status report, huh?
That's a tricky one.
They're not so much in the plaza
as they are inside the courthouse.
It's just awful. What?
Chief, Chief Justice, I have a report.
The pirates have cut through our
defenses and broken down the front door.
They're currently inside the courthouse.
We can see that already, fool.
Not as much resistance as I expected.
We should be able to tear right through.
What's that?
Whoa, what?
He's got three heads!
He's just like that dog that
guards the underworld. Marverous?
You mean Cerberus!
Order in the court, damn it!
This is a sacred chamber
of law, you hooligans!
You had the nerve to bust in here, so shut
up, sit still, and receive your sentence!
All right, guys.
You head to the roof and
join up with Straw Hat.
We'll stay here at the door with
Yokozuna and hold off the Marines.
We'll watch your back, so keep moving
and don't worry about the small fries.
You got it.
Hey, it looks like they're starting
some kind of trial over there.
Who cares? Just ignore them.
Which way do we go?
Straight ahead.
There are stairs on both sides.
Let's make our way to the top.
Right.
Hey!
They're ignoring the trial!
I know they're pirates, but seriously,
how rude can these guys get?
Bad bastards!
How dare you mock the Judicial Island!
I'll teach you some respect!
Are his sword spinning
or am I seeing things?
Charming demon.
Sleepless knight.
Is he the guy who broke the door?
Well that's that now
let's get moving right.
He puts all of us to shame and he's
not even the captain of their crew.
Hey hey hey wait out of the way reindeer
out of the way moss
head i'm coming through.
I forgot about him somebody's gotta protect
nami from all these bad guys and that
somebody's Gonna be me damn it no watch
it what why is he picking a fight now?
If you want to settle this, then bring it!
Shut up!
This is your fault for trying
to hog Nami all for yourself!
Follow me, Nami.
Forget about him.
Uh, hey.
We came to this place to
rescue Robin, remember?
Oh!
I bet she's waiting for me!
She's waiting for her prince to save her!
She's probably crying right now
because she misses me so much!
Whatever!
Come on!
Are you kidding me?!
Come back, Zoro!
That's the wrong way!
Are you sure?
How can you screw this up when the
stairs are right in front of your face?
What's wrong with you?
If you stopped giving such crappy
directions, this wouldn't happen.
You are not blaming this on me!
Zoro, I'll try to make you some medicine
later to fix your brain problem.
Brain problem?
Hey, Chopper, make some
for him while you're at it.
I'll try, but he may be beyond help.
I'm starting to have doubts
about this whole rescue thing.
They'll pull it together when
the going gets tough, I'm sure.
I mean, probably.
I mean, hopefully.
These are serious crimes.
Yes, they're quite grave indeed.
But we should show restraint and
sentence them to death. Agreed.
Think you can ignore
the Chief Justice, huh?
Chopper, Nami, go on ahead.
I'll make quick work of this thing
and catch up with you in a second.
No!
I'm a thing now, am I?
And easy to defeat, no less?
I'll teach you the meaning
of fear, you little...
Poo!
No, stop it!
He-ho-he-he-he!
You gotta go through us first, Cerberus.
Are you sure about this?
Huh. Let's go.
Uh, right.
Finally!
My face closed! Of course.
All open doors will eventually shut.
I'm amazed you still managed
to dodge my Tempest kick.
Yeah, no big deal.
How unsettling.
Check!
He's fast!
Finger pistol!
Change!
Fire buddy!
How come?
Fire!
Buddy!
He's completely keeping up with my speed.
He even changed the
course of my Tempest Kick.
His physical abilities are unbelievable.
It's no good. Hmm?
I can't stay like this.
It won't work.
I lost Aokiji.
I realized something.
I said to myself,
you keep running into guys
that are stronger and stronger,
unless you can get stronger too.
You can't protect your friends.
And I want to.
They're not all strong like me.
But either way, they're my
friends and I want to keep them.
So I have to get stronger
than anyone else.
Otherwise, there's a
chance I could lose them.
Then what are you going to do?
I thought of a new way to
fight with all my might.
So that I won't lose anyone.
So I won't let anyone slip away from me.
What's happening to him?
What's going on inside his body?
That did it.
You won't be able to stop me now What?
All my strength and techniques
just went up by one step
Second gear!
Thank
you so
much for watching.